Guide to the American Federation of State, County, and Municipal Employees (AFSCME), District Council 37 Records WAG.265
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series II: Executive Office Records, 1951-1999; 28490
  - Subseries II:B: Lillian Roberts Associate Director Records, 1951-1983., 28491
    - Bellevue Hospital Employees' Advisory Council, 1972; cuid4605; 28879 (Box 12, Folder 24)
    - Bio-Medical Equipment Technical Training Program, 1968-1971; cuid4606; 28878 (Box 12, Folder 25)
    - Blue Collar Division: Monthly Reports, May 1974-Sep 1974; cuid4607; 28877 (Box 12, Folder 26)
    - Blue Collar Division: Monthly Reports, Oct 1974-Feb 1975; cuid4608; 28876 (Box 12, Folder 27)
    - Blue Collar Division: Monthly Reports, Mar 1975-Nov 1975; cuid4609; 28875 (Box 12, Folder 28)
    - Blue Collar Locals: Citywide Strike, 1971; cuid4610; 28874 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Borough of Manhattan Community College Fund, 1976; cuid4611; 28873 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Bronx Municipal Hospital Center, 1976-1978; cuid4612; 28872 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Bryan (David E.) Fund, 1980; cuid4613; 28871 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Career Development and Training, 1968-1971; cuid4614; 28870 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Career Development and Training, 1972; cuid4615; 28869 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Career Development and Training: Hospitals I, 1967-1972; cuid4616; 28868 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Career Development and Training: Hospitals II, 1967-1972; cuid4617; 28867 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Career Development and Training: Hospitals III, 1967-1972; cuid4618; 28866 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Carver Federal Savings: Board of Directors, 1974-1981; cuid4619; 28865 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - CUNY: Career Programs, 1970-1972; cuid4620; 28864 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Clerical-Administrative Division: Monthly Reports, Apr 1974-Nov 1974; cuid4621; 28863 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Clerical-Administrative Division: Monthly Reports, Dec 1974-May 1975; cuid4622; 28862 (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Clerical-Administrative Division: Monthly Reports, Jun 1975-Dec 1975; cuid4623; 28861 (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - Coalition of Black Trade Unionists, 1973-1979; cuid4624; 28860 (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - Coalition of Concerned Citizens for Human Resources, 1974-1976; cuid4625; 28859 (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - Coalition of Trade Union Women, 1974-1978; cuid4626; 28858 (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - College of New Rochelle DC 37 Campus, New Resources Program, 1973-1975, 1978; cuid4627; 28857 (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - Committee of Interns and Residents, undated, 1975-1976; cuid4628; 28856 (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - Committee of Interns and Residents: Effects of Personnel Reductions in Hospitals, 1978; cuid4629; 28855 (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - Committee to Aid the Refugees of East Pakistan, 1971; cuid4630; 28854 (Box 13, Folder 21)
    - Community Mental Health Center, 1973-1974; cuid4631; 28853 (Box 13, Folder 22)
    - Community School Board Elections, 1974-1975; cuid4632; 28852 (Box 13, Folder 23)
    - Comprehensive Employment and Training Act (CETA), Oct 1978-Apr 1979; cuid4633; 28851 (Box 13, Folder 24)
    - CETA, May 1979-Jun 1979; cuid4634; 28850 (Box 13, Folder 25)
    - CETA, Jul 1979-Aug 1979; cuid4635; 28849 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - CETA, Sep 1979; cuid4636; 28848 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - CETA, Oct 1979-Mar 1980; cuid4637; 28847 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - CETA Questionnaire, 1979; cuid4638; 28846 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Contracting Out: Hospitals, 1975; cuid4639; 28845 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, 1970; cuid4640; 28844 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, Sep 1971-Dec 1971; cuid4641; 28843 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, Jan 1972-Mar 1972; cuid4642; 28842 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, Apr 10, 1972-Jun 1972; cuid4643; 28841 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, Jul 1972-Oct 1972; cuid4644; 28840 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, Oct 1972-Dec 1972; cuid4645; 28839 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence, Jan 1973-Jun 1973; cuid4646; 28838 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence, Jul 1973-Dec 1973; cuid4647; 28837 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence, Jan 1974-May 1974; cuid4648; 28836 (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence, Jun 1974-Dec 1974; cuid4649; 28835 (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence, 1975; cuid4650; 28834 (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence, Jan 1977-Jun 1977; cuid4651; 28833 (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence, Jul 1977-Dec 1977; cuid4652; 28832 (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence, Jan 1978-Mar 1978; cuid4653; 28831 (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence, Apr 1978-May 1978; cuid4654; 28830 (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence, Jun 1978; cuid4655; 28829 (Box 14, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence, Jul 1978-Dec 1978; cuid4656; 28828 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, Jan 1979-May 1979; cuid4657; 28827 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, Jun 1979-Sep 1979; cuid4658; 28826 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, Oct 1979-Dec 1979; cuid4659; 28825 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, 1980; cuid4660; 28824 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, Jan 1981-Feb 1981; cuid4661; 28823 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, Mar 1981-Jun 1981; cuid4662; 28822 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Coney Island Hospital, 1976-1979; cuid4663; 28821 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Cost of Living Adjustment (COLA): Clerical Division, ca.1975; cuid4664; 28820 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Council for the Advancement of Experiential Learning (CAEL), 1977-1980; cuid4665; 28819 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Cumberland Hospital, 1975-1978; cuid4666; 28818 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Cumberland Hospital Mental Health Service, 1974; cuid4667; 28817 (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Daycare Programs, 1970-1972; cuid4668; 28816 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Delafield Hospital: Action to Prevent Closing, 1975; cuid4669; 28815 (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - Delafield Hospital: Legal Papers, 1975; cuid4670; 28814 (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - Democratic National Convention, 1976; cuid4671; 28813 (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - Democratic National Party Conference: Platform Advisory Committee, 1979; cuid4672; 28812 (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - Education Fund, 1970-1971; cuid4673; 28811 (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - Education Fund, 1976-1979; cuid4674; 28810 (Box 15, Folder 19)
    - Educational Guidance Center for the Retarded, 1971; cuid4675; 28809 (Box 15, Folder 20)
    - Emergency Employment Act of 1971 I, 1971-1974; cuid4676; 28808 (Box 15, Folder 21)
    - Emergency Employment Act of 1971 II, 1971-1974; cuid4677; 28807 (Box 15, Folder 22)
    - Emergency Medical Services: Safety Conditions and Training, 1972-1976; cuid4678; 28806 (Box 15, Folder 23)
    - Executive Staff, 1972; cuid4679; 28805 (Box 15, Folder 24)
    - Federation of Field Representatives, 1969-1972; cuid4680; 28804 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Federation of Field Representatives, 1975-1981; cuid4681; 28803 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Federation of Field Representatives: Agreements, 1970-1980; cuid4682; 28802 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Feed the Hungry Drive, 1974; cuid4683; 28801 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Fiscal Crisis: Budget Meetings with City Departments, 1976; cuid4684; 28800 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Fordham Hospital, undated, 1976; cuid4685; 28799 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Ghetto Medicine Program (New York State), 1977-1978; cuid4686; 28798 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Goldwater Hospital Parking Facility Closing, 1973-1974; cuid4687; 28797 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Gouverneur Hospital, 1975-1976; cuid4688; 28796 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Gouverneur Hospital, 1977-1978; cuid4689; 28795 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Harlem Hospital, 1975-1979; cuid4690; 28794 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Harlem Hospital: Community-Worker Board, 1969; cuid4691; 28793 (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - Health and Security Plan: Option IV, 1976-1978; cuid4692; 28792 (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - Help Our Own Fund (for laid-off members), 1975-1976; cuid4693; 28791 (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - High Risk Premature Infant Technician Training Program, 1970-1971; cuid4694; 28790 (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - HIP of Greater New York, 1972; cuid4695; 28789 (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - Home Attendants, 1977-1978; cuid4696; 28788 (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - Hospital Closings and Layoffs, 1976; cuid4697; 28787 (Box 16, Folder 18)
    - Hospitals Division: Monthly Reports, Apr 1974-Nov 1974; cuid4698; 28786 (Box 16, Folder 19)
    - Housekeeping Aid Sanitation Training Program, 1971-1972; cuid4699; 28785 (Box 16, Folder 20)
    - I Paid My Dues (labor play), 1976; cuid4700; 28784 (Box 16, Folder 21)
    - International Conference on Trends in Industrial Relations (Tel Aviv, Israel), 1971; cuid4701; 28783 (Box 16, Folder 22)
    - Interns, 1972; cuid4702; 28782 (Box 16, Folder 23)
    - Invitations, 1970-1971; cuid4703; 28781 (Box 16, Folder 24)
    - Just One Break (JOB), 1977; cuid4704; 28780 (Box 16, Folder 25)
    - King, Martin Luther, Jr.: DC 37 Response to Assassination and Tributes, 1968-1978; cuid4705; 28779 (Box 16, Folder 26)
    - Kings County Hospital Center, 1973-1978; cuid4706; 28778 (Box 16, Folder 27)
    - Kings County Hospital Center: Attitudinal Program, 1972; cuid4707; 28777 (Box 16, Folder 28)
    - Legal Internship and Training Education (LITE) Program: Bedford Stuyvesant Lawyers Association, 1977-1978; cuid4708; 28776 (Box 16, Folder 29)
    - Legal Services Proposal, 1972; cuid4709; 28775 (Box 16, Folder 30)
    - Legislative Information, 1969-1971, 1978; cuid4710; 28774 (Box 16, Folder 31)
    - Lincoln Hospital, 1971-1978; cuid4711; 28773 (Box 16, Folder 32)
    - Local 154 (Amalgamated Professional Employees), 1979-1980; cuid4712; 28772 (Box 16, Folder 33)
    - Local 371 (SSEU), 1969-1971; cuid4713; 28771 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Local 371(SSEU), 1975-1976; cuid4714; 28770 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Local 371 (SSEU), 1977-1981; cuid4715; 28769 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Local 371 (SSEU): Contract, 1969-1970; cuid4716; 28768 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Local 371 (SSEU): Dental Assistants, 1968-1971; cuid4717; 28767 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Local 371 (SSEU): Homemakers and Housekeepers, 1968-1971; cuid4718; 28766 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Local 372 (Board of Education), 1970-1971; cuid4719; 28765 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Local 372 (Board of Education), 1975; cuid4720; 28764 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Local 372 (Board of Education), 1976-1981; cuid4721; 28763 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Local 372 (Board of Education): Career Training Programs, 1970-1971; cuid4722; 28762 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Local 372 (Board of Education): Hourly Workers, 1970-1971; cuid4723; 28761 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Local 372 (Board of Education): New York Archdiocese Schools, 1970-1971; cuid4724; 28760 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Local 372 (Board of Education): Para-Professionals, 1969; cuid4725; 28759 (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - Local 374 (Quasi-Public Employees), 1978; cuid4726; 28758 (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - Local 375 (CSTG), 1975-1976; cuid4727; 28757 (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - Local 375 (CSTG), 1977-1980; cuid4728; 28756 (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - Local 384 (CUNY): Gittelson Employees, 1951-1980; cuid4729; 28755 (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - Local 420 (Municipal Hospital Employees Union), 1966-1967; cuid4730; 28754 (Box 17, Folder 18)
    - Local 420 (Municipal Hospital Employees Union), Jan 1968-Apr 1968; cuid4731; 28753 (Box 17, Folder 19)
    - Local 420 (Municipal Hospital Employees Union), May 1968-Jul 1968; cuid4732; 28752 (Box 17, Folder 20)
    - Local 420 (Municipal Hospital Employees Union), Aug 1968-Dec 1968; cuid4733; 28751 (Box 17, Folder 21)
    - Local 420 (Municipal Hospital Employees Union), Jan 1969-May 1969; cuid4734; 28750 (Box 17, Folder 22)
    - Local 420 (Municipal Hospital Employees Union), Jun 1969-Dec 1969; cuid4735; 28749 (Box 17, Folder 23)
    - Local 420 (Municipal Hospital Employees Union), 1970; cuid4736; 28748 (Box 17, Folder 24)
    - Local 420 (Municipal Hospital Employees Union), 1975; cuid4737; 28747 (Box 17, Folder 25)
    - Local 420 (Municipal Hospital Employees Union), 1975-1976; cuid4738; 28746 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Local 420 (Municipal Hospital Employees Union), 1977-Aug 1980; cuid4739; 28745 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Local 420 (Municipal Hospital Employees Union), Sep 1980-Apr 1981; cuid4740; 28744 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Local 420 (Municipal Hospital Employees Union): Ambulance Technicians, 1969-1972; cuid4741; 28743 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Local 420 (Municipal Hospital Employees Union): James Butler Dispute, 1978-1980; cuid4742; 28742 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Local 420 (Municipal Hospital Employees Union): James Butler Dispute, Petitions and Legal Papers, 1978-1979; cuid4743; 28741 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Local 420 (Municipal Hospital Employees Union): Bonano v. Butler, Release Time Information, 1976-1979; cuid4744; 28740 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Local 420 (Municipal Hospital Employees Union): Delegates Election I, 1980; cuid4745; 28739 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Local 420 (Municipal Hospital Employees Union): Delegates Election II, 1980; cuid4746; 28738 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Local 420 (Municipal Hospital Employees Union): Dietary Aide Training Program, 1968-1971; cuid4747; 28737 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Local 420 (Municipal Hospital Employees Union): History, 1974; cuid4748; 28736 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Local 420 (Municipal Hospital Employees Union): Mortuary Caretakers, 1974-1975; cuid4749; 28735 (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Local 420 (Municipal Hospital Employees Union): Roosevelt Island Parking, 1973-1977; cuid4750; 28734 (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Local 420 (Municipal Hospital Employees Union): Uniform Committee, 1970-1972; cuid4751; 28733 (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - Local 768 (Health Services Employees), 1979-1980; cuid4752; 28732 (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - Local 957 (New York City Housing Authority Clericals), 1975-1979; cuid4753; 28731 (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - Local 1070 (Court, County and Department of Probation Employees), 1973-1977; cuid4754; 28730 (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - Local 1219 (Real Estate Employees): Housing Relocation Aides, 1971, 1978; cuid4755; 28729 (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - Local 1321 (Queens Library Guild), 1976; cuid4756; 28728 (Box 18, Folder 19)
    - Local 1359 (Rent Regulation Services Employees), 1980; cuid4757; 28727 (Box 18, Folder 20)
    - Local 1457 (Juvenile Center): Counselors, 1970, 1977-1980; cuid4758; 28726 (Box 18, Folder 21)
    - Local 1485 (Anti-Poverty Employees), 1969-1971; cuid4759; 28725 (Box 18, Folder 22)
    - Local 1485 (Anti-Poverty Employees): Fort Greene Community Corporation, 1969-1970; cuid4760; 28724 (Box 18, Folder 23)
    - Local 1485 (Anti-Poverty Employees): Hunts Point Community Corporation, 1969-1970; cuid4761; 28723 (Box 18, Folder 24)
    - Local 1485 (Anti-Poverty Employees): Lower West Side Community Corporation, 1969-1970; cuid4762; 28722 (Box 18, Folder 25)
    - Local 1485 (Anti-Poverty Employees): Qualicap's Health and Welfare Action Center, 1970; cuid4763; 28721 (Box 18, Folder 26)
    - Local 1485 (Anti-Poverty Employees): South Bronx Community Corporation, 1969-1970; cuid4764; 28720 (Box 18, Folder 27)
    - Local 1485 (Anti-Poverty Employees): South Brooklyn and Red Hook Community Corporations, 1969-1970; cuid4765; 28719 (Box 18, Folder 28)
    - Local 1485 (Anti-Poverty Employees): Southeast Queens Community Corporation, 1970; cuid4766; 28718 (Box 18, Folder 29)
    - Local 1503 (Metropolitan Museum of Art), 1979; cuid4767; 28717 (Box 18, Folder 30)
    - Local 1509 (Youth Board Employees), 1972-1980; cuid4768; 28716 (Box 18, Folder 31)
    - Local 1549 (Clerical-Administrative Employees), undated, 1978-1981; cuid4769; 28715 (Box 18, Folder 32)
    - Local 1549 (Clerical-Administrative Employees): Police Department, 1977-1980; cuid4770; 28714 (Box 18, Folder 33)
    - Local 1597 (Custodial Assistant Employees), 1972-1980; cuid4771; 28713 (Box 18, Folder 34)
    - Local 1931 (TBTA Maintenance Employees), 1980-1981; cuid4772; 28712 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Local 2021 (Off-Track Betting Corporation, OTB), Dec 1974-Mar 1975; cuid4773; 28711 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Local 2021 (OTB), Apr 1975-Dec 1975; cuid4774; 28710 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Local 2021 (OTB), 1976-1979; cuid4775; 28709 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Local 2507 (Ambulance Corpsmen), 1970-1973; cuid4776; 28708 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Local 2507 (Ambulance Corpsmen), 1974-1976; cuid4777; 28707 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Local 2507 (Ambulance Corpsmen), 1977-1980; cuid4778; 28706 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Local 2627 (New York City Electronic Data Processing Employees), 1978-1980; cuid4779; 28705 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - March on Washington (labor coalition), 1975; cuid4780; 28704 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Mayor's Midtown Citizens Committee, 1976; cuid4781; 28703 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Medical Surgical Technician Training Program, 1971; cuid4782; 28702 (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Membership Gain/Loss Records and Dues Check-off Reports, 1969-1972; cuid4783; 28701 (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Methadone Maintenance Treatment Program, 1971; cuid4784; 28700 (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - Metropolitan Hospital, 1979; cuid4785; 28699 (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - Minority Advisory Committee to Secretary of U. S. Department of Health, Education, and Welfare, 1978; cuid4786; 28698 (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - Mobilization for Youth: "Establishing a New Career, The Social Health Technician", 1970; cuid4787; 28697 (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - Mobilization for Youth: New Occupations Demonstration Project, 1969; cuid4788; 28696 (Box 19, Folder 17)
    - Mobilization for Youth: Social Health and Psychiatric Technician Training Program, 1970-1971; cuid4789; 28695 (Box 19, Folder 18)
    - Morrisania City Hospital, 1976-1977; cuid4790; 28694 (Box 19, Folder 19)
    - Municipal Credit Union, 1974-Jun 1977; cuid4791; 28693 (Box 19, Folder 20)
    - Municipal Credit Union, Jul 1977-Dec 1977; cuid4792; 28692 (Box 19, Folder 21)
    - Municipal Credit Union, 1978; cuid4793; 28691 (Box 19, Folder 22)
    - Municipal Credit Union: Advisory Committee, 1978-1979; cuid4794; 28690 (Box 19, Folder 23)
    - Municipal Employees Legal Service Fund (MELS), 1973-1980; cuid4795; 28689 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - National Association of Health Services Executives, 1977; cuid4796; 28688 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - National Child Labor Committee: Board of Trustees, 1979-1980; cuid4797; 28687 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - National Science Foundation Research Project: "Relations Among Work Organization, Job Satisfaction, and Productivity", 1973-1974; cuid4798; 28686 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - New York City: "A Plan for Improving the Effectiveness of Hospital Services…" I, 1979; cuid4799; 28685 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - New York City: "A Plan for Improving the Effectiveness of Hospital Services…" II, 1979; cuid4800; 28684 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - New York City: "Plan for Localized Government", 1972; cuid4801; 28683 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - New York City Agency for Child Development, 1971-1974; cuid4802; 28682 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - New York City Board of Education: Addiction Prevention Program Instructors (Local 372), 1974-1975; cuid4803; 28681 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - New York City Department of Hospitals, 1967; cuid4804; 28680 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - New York City HHC, 1969-1970; cuid4805; 28679 (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - New York City HHC, 1971; cuid4806; 28678 (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - New York City HHC, 1972-1974; cuid4807; 28677 (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - New York City HHC, Jan 1975-Jun 1975; cuid4808; 28676 (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - New York City HHC, Jul 1975-Dec 1975; cuid4809; 28675 (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - New York City HHC, Jan 1976-Mar 1976; cuid4810; 28674 (Box 20, Folder 16)
    - New York City HHC, Apr 1976-May 1976; cuid4811; 28673 (Box 20, Folder 17)
    - New York City HHC, Jun 1976-Aug 1976; cuid4812; 28672 (Box 20, Folder 18)
    - New York City HHC, Sep 1976-Dec 1976; cuid4813; 28671 (Box 20, Folder 19)
    - New York City HHC, Jan 1977-May 1977; cuid4814; 28670 (Box 20, Folder 20)
    - New York City HHC, Jun 1977-Oct 1977; cuid4815; 28669 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - New York City HHC, Nov 1977-Dec 1977; cuid4816; 28668 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - New York City HHC, Jan 1978-Apr 1978; cuid4817; 28667 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - New York City HHC, May 1978-Sep 1978; cuid4818; 28666 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - New York City HHC, Oct 1978-Dec 1978; cuid4819; 28665 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - New York City HHC, Jan 1979; cuid4820; 28664 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - New York City HHC, Feb 1979-Mar 1979; cuid4821; 28663 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - New York City HHC, Apr 1979; cuid4822; 28662 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - New York City HHC, May 1979; cuid4823; 28661 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - New York City HHC, Jun 1979-Jul 1979; cuid4824; 28660 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - New York City HHC, Aug 1979-Oct 1979; cuid4825; 28659 (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - New York City HHC, Nov 1979-Dec 1979; cuid4826; 28658 (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - New York City HHC, Jan 1980-Feb 1980; cuid4827; 28657 (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - New York City HHC, Mar 1980-May 1980; cuid4828; 28656 (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - New York City HHC, Jun 1980-Oct 1980; cuid4829; 28655 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - New York City HHC, Nov 1980-Dec 1980; cuid4830; 28654 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - New York City HHC, 1981; cuid4831; 28653 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - New York City HHC: Ad Hoc Panel on Threatened Strike ("Patterson Panel" and Tri-Partite Task Force on Proposed Layoffs), 1976; cuid4832; 28652 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - New York City HHC: Affiliation of Municipal and Voluntary Hospitals, 1968-Feb 1971; cuid4833; 28651 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - New York City HHC: Affiliation of Municipal and Voluntary Hospitals, Mar 1971-1972; cuid4834; 28650 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - New York City HHC: Affiliation of Municipal and Voluntary Hospitals, 1973-1975; cuid4835; 28649 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - New York City HHC: Affiliation of Municipal and Voluntary Hospitals, Contracts and Financial Records, Jul 1970-Feb 1972; cuid4836; 28648 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - New York City HHC: Affiliation of Municipal and Voluntary Hospitals, Contracts and Financial Records, Apr 1972-Apr 1975; cuid4837; 28647 (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - New York City HHC: Affiliation of Municipal and Voluntary Hospitals, Crisis Budget Information, 1974-Apr 1975; cuid4838; 28646 (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - New York City HHC: Affiliation of Municipal and Voluntary Hospitals, Crisis Budget Information, undated, May 1975-Sep 1975; cuid4839; 28645 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - New York City HHC: Affiliation of Municipal and Voluntary Hospitals, Employee List, ca.1972; cuid4840; 28644 (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - New York City HHC: Affiliation of Municipal and Voluntary Hospitals, Publicity, 1972-1975; cuid4841; 28643 (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - New York City HHC: Affirmative Action Plan, 1973-1974; cuid4842; 28642 (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - New York City HHC: Bellevue Hospital Labor/Management Productivity Committee Report, 1977; cuid4843; 28641 (Box 22, Folder 15)
    - New York City HHC: Board of Directors (Budget crisis), 1975; cuid4844; 28640 (Box 22, Folder 16)
    - New York City HHC: Bronx Hospitals (Budget crisis), 1975; cuid4845; 28639 (Box 22, Folder 17)
    - New York City HHC: Brooklyn Hospitals (Budget crisis), 1974; cuid4846; 28638 (Box 22, Folder 18)
    - New York City HHC: Brooklyn Regionalization Program, 1977-1980; cuid4847; 28637 (Box 22, Folder 19)
    - New York City HHC: Budget Crisis, 1974-1975; cuid4848; 28636 (Box 22, Folder 20)
    - New York City HHC: Budget Crisis, CHP Reports, 1975; cuid4849; 28635 (Box 22, Folder 21)
    - New York City HHC: Clerical Division, 1970-1971; cuid4850; 28634 (Box 22, Folder 22)
    - New York City HHC: Clippings, 1970-1975; cuid4851; 28633 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - New York City HHC: Community Boards, 1970-1971; cuid4852; 28632 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - New York City HHC: Education and Training, 1973-1974; cuid4853; 28631 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - New York City HHC: Education and Training, 1976; cuid4854; 28630 (Box 23, Folder 4)